ORI
Kame-chan.
Kame-chan?
Kame-chan!
You're next, Kame-chan.
Sorry, sorry. I zoned out.
Then let's get to it...
Othello-kun.
Finally.
Togame-san, we've been waiting for you!
- Get 'im!
- Kill him!
The cheers are quite loud.
Nothing so far compares to this.
One punch. One punch!
Oh, S-Sakura-san.
P-Please be careful.
Try not to die.
Countin' on ya.
Sakura.
Go have a nice long talk.
A fight is a "conversation,"
Sakura-kun.
Can I even do such a thing?
In any case...
It's not just the uplifting feeling
when I fight a tough opponent.
I don't know what this is.
Well...
As for tomorrow
I'm counting on all of you!
I did say leave it to me.
Let's hurry up and do this.
No need to rush so much...
It's not bad to be fast...
but sometimes
it feels a bit lacking, right?
Especially right now...
I want to take my time and enjoy this.
Sakura, I can tell you're pretty good
after watching you fight the last two days.
But you know...
Togame is keeping the Shishitoren,
the devotees of power, at bay.
And that's because he has
that much strength in him.
You said you wanted to go slow,
but you can move pretty quickly.
Oh? Was that fast?
I'll stay at this speed.
You'll slowly play along with me.
Bring it.
I'll play along as much as you want.
I-It's all Sakura-san can do to dodge?
Well, Togame and Tomiyama
always have stood out in Shishitoren.
And that means...
He's in a different class
compared to the previous three.
Well, I'm sure he's the one
feeling it the most as the opponent.
H-He did it.
You're already keeping up?
How skillful.
Othello-kun, you said I was pretty lame
back at the tunnel.
That really irritated me.
You're so irritating...
with how you speak and all.
Way to go, Togame-san.
Get 'im!
He's still as dangerous as ever.
Kame-chan! Kame-chan!
Huh? You're already out cold?
Your current self
is a lot lamer than me.
Saying whatever you want to people,
and acting cocky.
Only people with power can be like that.
You can act smug because
you're within a strong pack, yeah?
Like when the glass bell
of a wind chime breaks, it falls silent...
When you're alone,
you don't have a voice, do you?
Come on, I'm still talking...
What you say is indeed true.
Freedom is given
only to those with power.
Without power...
you can't push through with who you are.
But in your eyes,
I look like one of them.
Like one of the people...
I hate the most.
In that case...
I can't lose to you even if it kills me.
Wh-What's up with that guy?
He suddenly...
I-I knew that Sakura-san was strong.
But was he this strong?
Come on, what's gotten into ya?
If you're gonna lose against me,
that means what you said
was all a mistake.
According to your logic
with that so-called devotion,
that's what this means.
Don't get cocky,
you damn brat!
So-called devotion?
What do you know about the Shishitoren?
Everyone here
always strives for higher ground.
They swear to push through
with who they are.
That is "devotion to power."
Compared to you superhero wannabes...
the weight of our "power" is greater.
Oh, he won't get back up.
That's what happens
when you go against Togame-san.
S-Sakura-san. No way...
It's not over yet.
I said, what you're mouthing off...
isn't what you're doin'.
Just change your name...
to "The Bully Club."
Stop talking already.
You pummel guys
who are already down.
You chase around middle school kids.
I can't lose to guys like you!
What're you talking about?
I know nothing about that.
I see.
So that's why you guys were there.
Gimme a second, 'kay?
Honestly, I was wondering...
why Furin was on our turf for no reason.
What the hell were you guys doing there?
Answer me.
W-We saw a middle school kid
we didn't recognize, so we were playing with him.
B-But it was Saruwatari
who first suggested it.
Sheesh, Kame-chan, enough of that.
Hurry on up and get back to it.
Things were just getting good.
Hey, sorry 'bout that.
Thanks for waiting.
Let's continue... where we left off.
Whoa, that was amazing!
You defeated all of them by yourself?
You're strong.
How about it? Wanna join our team?
What are you talking...
We're called Shishitoren.
No, I said...
I just joined them myself.
But I'm sure you'll like it.
I said, just hold on...
Come on, let's go.
I'll introduce you to everyone.
That was how I met Choji.
Do you know what
"devotion to power" means?
Hey, hey. Kame-chan. Kame-chan,
are you listening? Do you know?
I'm listening, and I do know.
I heard it in the beginning.
Hey, you know, it's an oath to push through
who you are, unyielding to anyone else.
How you don't listen to others
never changes.
And power is something you use
to become free.
ORI
The newbie who just joined is amazing.
Yeah, I heard.
I heard that pair went into zinc's territory
by themselves and pummeled them all down.
The rumors about them are everywhere.
We're back.
I punched them around
as payback for you, Numa-chan.
Th-Thanks.
Y-You seriously went over there?
You guys are amazing.
HMPH
Of course. I'm trying to be
the freest guy ever.
I can't be losing at a place like that.
Uh, well...
When we first joined the team, they taught us
that power is a means to be free.
So, the strongest guy...
is also the most free. So he said.
Right?
Yup, yup.
Doesn't it sound fun to be the freest guy?
I'm racing with Kame-chan to see
which one of us will get there first.
All you guys should race with us.
Back then, Choji was strong and seemed
to have more fun than anyone else.
He was like the sun, embodying
the concept of our devotion.
Choji said it was a race between us,
but I had no intention of racing at all.
I always was bad at hanging around people.
But when I was with Choji,
I could enter the social circle.
It was fun.
I felt like I was free.
I thought that the team would be
even better if Choji became the leader.
I really thought that.
Choji?
What's wrong?
You should go inside and—
Hey, Kame-chan.
I became the leader, didn't I?
Yeah.
And the leader is the strongest
and the freest, right?
Yeah.
It's not...
fun at all.
So I had a thought.
I just need the entire team
to be as strong as I am.
Oh, okay.
You're going to train everyone.
I think that's a good idea.
I'll go inside and talk to everyone—
Tomiyama-san. Togame-san.
This guy got assaulted
by guys calling themselves zinc.
Zinc? Them again.
Let's go, Choji...
You came right back after being defeated?
Could you not?
You won't get stronger that way.
That means you can't be free,
and it's not fun.
Weak guys....
are not wanted in Shishitoren.
Isn't that right, Kame-chan?
Why?
Why does it end up that way?
Doing that won't make them stronger—
I'm the leader, right?
I'm the strongest. I'm free.
I won't yield to anyone.
I'm going to decide.
If you don't understand me,
then get out.
Fine.
But...
I'll tell everyone
about your views, Choji.
I'll do all the "skinning" too.
So Choji....
please keep smiling with the guys.
I decided I would get covered in mud.
The sun must be loved by everyone.
Even if it meant binding everyone
with power to become free,
I will keep the current Shishitoren going.
Until the day...
the sun shows itself again.
Hey, are you serious?
No way.
You're not being serious, are you?
Huh? That's not—
You don't wanna land that punch.
You don't wanna dodge my kick, either.
What the hell are you tryin' to do?
Really...
What am I trying to do?
FIGHT TO WIN
Togame-san's geta clogs
made an impact noise
that didn't even sound like wood.
Judging from how it felt on my head,
there wasn't any metal in there.
You can tell with your head?
Well, I've taken blows
to my head from many things.
For instance...
Huh? For instance?
This.
This?
Or this.
And this, too.
I'm scared.